（男の子）
どこ行っちゃったんだろうね？
（女の子）
ねえどこ行っちゃったんだろうね
He may be lost
somewhere like I was.
（梨花(りか)）ボクと同じで
きっと どこかで迷子なのですよ
（ﾚﾅ）ま…迷子いいね
Being lost sounds nice.
はぅ～！お持ち帰り～！
（梨花）み～…
Oh, I want to take you home!
He's old, right? Maybe he's
just wandering around senilely?
（圭一(けいいち)）じいさんなんだろう？
ボケちゃって
徘徊(はいかい)してるだけじゃないのか？
The village headman
is a lively person...
（沙都子(さとこ)）村長さんは―
お習字も剣道も教える
ハツラツとした方でございますわよ
...who teaches
calligraphy and kendo.
じゃどうしたんだ？
Then what happened?
まさかオヤシロさまのたたりにでも
遭ったっていうのか？
Are you saying it's
Oyashiro-sama's curse?
The village headman...
（圭一）昨日の昼過ぎ村長さんは
会合で神社の集会所へ出かけた
...left for a meeting at the shrine's
meeting room past noon yesterday.
And the meeting
ended well after sunset.
そして日がどっぷり暮れたころに
その会合はお開きになった
それっきり
村長さんの姿を見た人はいない
No one has seen
the village headman since.
- "Cotton Drifting" Chapter -
Episode 03: LIES
When They Cry
Furimuita sono ushiro no
(shoumen dare)?
Kurayami ni tsume wo tatete
(yoru wo hikisaita).
Amadare wa chi no shizuku to
natte nodo wo tsutai ochiru.
Mou dokonimo kaeru
basho ga nai nara...
...kono yubi tomare
watashi no yubi ni.
Sono yubi goto tsuretette ageru.
Higurashi ga naku
akazu no mori e.
Atomodori wa mou dekinai.
（圭一）
これで５年連続オヤシロさまの
たたりが起こったことになる
So Oyashiro-sama's curse
occurred five straight years.
Do you believe in curses?
（鷹野(たかの)）たたりを信じるかしら？
If it's caused by people, the
culprit's likely from Hinamizawa.
（詩音(しおん)）人間の仕業なら
雛見沢(ひなみざわ)の誰かが犯人なんでしょうね
If it's the curse, Shion and I,
who entered the ritual tool shrine...
たたりなら祭具殿に
入った俺と詩音のはずなのに
なんだ梨花ちゃんか
Oh, Rika-chan.
梨花ちゃん？
Rika-chan? Did you fall down?
転んだのか？
No.
違うのです…違うのです
一体何があったんだ？
Then what happened?
ボクのことはいいのです
Don't mind me.
それよりも
（圭一）ハッ…
Before that...
お祭りの晩に
何か悪いことしましたか？
Did you do something
bad on festival night?
Keiichi?
（梨花）圭一？
Sorry for asking
you a strange thing.
変なこと聞いてごめんなさいです
忘れてくださいなのですよ
Please forget about it.
り…梨花ちゃん
R-Rika-chan.
（圭一）言ってしまいたい…
I want to say it.
でも梨花ちゃんは
あの神社の巫女(みこ)さんで
But she's the shrine
maiden of that shrine.
She'd be the one who'd never
forgive people breaking the taboo.
禁忌を破ったことを
いちばん許さない立場にある人間
On festival night...
（梨花）お祭りの晩
（圭一）あっ…
神社の祭具殿に
猫さんが入り込んだそうです
...I heard a cat went inside
the ritual tool shrine.
ね…猫？
A-A cat?
はい猫さんです
ニャ～ニャ～なのです
Yes, a cat.
Meow, meow.
猫さんは中を見て
怖くなってびっくり仰天
The cat saw what's inside
and got scared and surprised.
一目散(いちもくさん)に逃げ出して
It ran out full speed and
keeps on shaking and meowing.
ガタガタブルブルニャ～ニャ～で
大変なのです
そ…その“猫さん”は
これからどうすればいい？
W-What should
that cat do from now on?
Mi?
The dog watched as
the mischievous cat went inside.
猫さんがいたずら心で
忍び込んだのを犬さんが見てたんだ
猫さんの所に
代わる代わるやって来ては―
They keep taking
turns asking the cat...
“忍び込んだだろう”って
問いただしてくるんだ
...whether or not it had snuck in.
大丈夫ですよ
猫さんはボクが守ってあげます
It'll be all right. I'll protect the cat.
何匹かの犬さんが―
It could be that some dogs
may have just misunderstood.
きっと勘違いしているだけなのだと
思います
ちょっと大変ですけど
頑張りますですよ
It'll be a little tough,
but I'll do my best.
ファイトオー！…なのです
Leave it up to me!
But the older sister cat is upset.
だけど…
姉猫は とても怒っています
妹猫が悪いことをしたので
とても怒っています
Since the little sister cat did
a bad thing, she's really upset.
今日から部活はなしにしましょう
（圭一）えっ？
Let's not have club
meetings starting today.
しばらくの間姉猫をそっと
してあげてほしいからなのです
I want the older sister cat
to be left alone for some time.
“姉猫”って魅音(みおん)のことか？
Older sister cat? Mion?
Keiichi, if the mistaken dog
that bit the village headman...
（梨花）圭一…村長さんを
かんだ勘違いの犬さんが―
猫さんにかみつこうとしたら
知らせてくださいね
...tries to bite the cat,
please let me know.
（圭一）
俺はその夜例え話とはいえ―
That night,
even metaphorically...
梨花ちゃんに洗いざらい
話してしまったことを後悔していた
...I regretted telling
Rika-chan everything.
梨花ちゃんの話は不可解だった
Her story was incomprehensible.
それだけじゃない　まるで
当事者のように詳しく語っていた
That's not all.
She spoke like she
was there, in such detail.
（伊知郎(いちろう)）
圭一電話だぞ園崎(そのざき)さんから
Keiichi, phone.
It's Sonozaki-san.
Hello?
もしもし
（詩音）詩音です
It's Shion.
詩音！その…
昨日はすまなかったつい興奮して
Shion!
Um, I'm sorry about yesterday.
I just got carried away.
（詩音）ハァ…
俺も詩音も同じ立場なんだよな
We're in the same situation.
一方的に責めるような
言い方をして悪かった
I'm sorry for talking
like you were to blame.
If you regret it, I'll forgive you.
後悔したなら許してあげます
（圭一）ハァ…
これからはお互いに
何か気になることがあったら―
From now on, let's inform
each other of our concerns.
報告し合いましょう
私たちは運命共同体なんです
We share a common destiny.
Yeah, I got it.
ああ分かった
Um, is it true that gramps
Kimiyoshi went missing?
あの…公由(きみよし)のおじいちゃんが
行方不明になったって本当ですか？
えっ公由？
Kimiyoshi?
ああ村長さんのことか
うんどうやらそうらしいけど
Oh, the village headman?
Yeah, so I heard.
詩音は知らなかったのか？
You didn't know?
Yes, what should I do?
はいどうしよう…
私昨日村長さんに―
Yesterday, I told the village
headman about that night.
あの晩のことを打ち明けたんです
（圭一）えっ！
私のせいです…
It's my fault!
Stop it. It's not your fault.
よせよ詩音のせいじゃないよ
No, it's my fault!
いいえ私のせいなんです！
だって打ち明けてすぐなんですよ
Because it happened right after.
He disappeared that night.
その晩すぐに消えてしまって…
話したから殺されてしまったんだ
打ち明けたから殺されてしまった…
Killed because I told him.
Killed because
I told him everything.
話したから殺されてしまった
Killed because I told him.
知ってしまったから
殺されてしまった…
Killed because he found out.
Killed because
I told him everything.
打ち明けたから―
殺されてしまった…
俺も…
Me too...
I also told Rika.
俺も梨花ちゃんに話したんだ
梨花ちゃん！
Rika-chan!
（レナのはなうた）
（ﾚﾅの父）お～いレナ電話だぞ
Hey, Rena. Phone call.
It's Keiichi-kun.
圭一君って子から
（ﾚﾅ）えっ？
（ﾚﾅ）もう一度確認するね
梨花ちゃんの家に電話したんだよね
Let me confirm this once more.
You called Rika's home, right?
And you're worried because
there's no answer, right?
それでどうしても
つながらないから心配なんだよね？
あ…ああ
10分以上は鳴らしてたと思う
Y-Yeah, I think it rang
for about ten minutes.
Her home isn't that big.
梨花ちゃんの家は
そんなに広くないの
Satoko's there too, so there's
no way they couldn't hear it.
沙都子ちゃんもいるんだから
気づかないはずないし
Hey!
（魅音）お～い！レナ圭ちゃん
Rena! Kei-chan!
Anyway, let's go.
とにかく行ってみよう
（圭一）う…うん
（ﾚﾅ）ない…おかしいよ
（圭一）どうした？レナ
- Not there. Strange.
- What's wrong, Rena?
梨花ちゃんと沙都子ちゃんは―
Rika-chan and Satoko-chan
always park their bikes here.
いつも ここに
自転車を止めているはずなのに
梨花ちゃん沙都子ちゃんいる？
Rika-chan! Satoko-chan!
Are you there?
梨花ちゃん沙都子ちゃん！
鍵がかかってる
It's locked.
２階の窓とかは？
窓が開いてるかもしれない
What about the second-floor
windows? They might be open.
- Kei-chan, ladder.
- Okay.
（魅音）圭ちゃんハシゴ
（圭一）おう
私本家のほう見てくるね
（圭一）本家？
I'll check the main house.
Main house?
The Furude main house.
（魅音）古手(ふるで)家の本家だよ
I heard it's been left alone
since Rika's parents died.
梨花ちゃんの両親が亡くなって以来
ずっと放置してあるそうだけど
あっそうか
梨花ちゃんの両親って…
Oh, right.
Rika's parents...
Satoko's too.
（魅音）沙都子もだよ
オヤシロさまのたたりってことで
両親が崖から落っこちて
Her parents fell off a cliff due
to Oyashiro-sama's curse...
お兄さんの悟史(さとし)君も
いなくなっちゃって…
...and her brother
Satoshi went missing.
それ以来梨花ちゃんと沙都子は
ここで一緒に暮らしてるんだよ
Since then, they've been
living here together.
２人とも大変なんだな
It must be hard on them.
She's cursed.
呪われてるんだよ
（圭一）えっ？
呪われてるって言ったの
（圭一）なっ…
I said she's cursed.
（ハシゴの揺れる音）
み…魅音？
M-Mion?
Satoko Hojo is a cursed child
with Oyashiro-sama's curse.
北条(ほうじょう)沙都子はね
オヤシロさまのたたりを
一身に受けた呪われた子なの
Satoshi-kun was working
so hard for his only sister...
悟史君も
たったひとりの妹のあの子のために
身を粉にして頑張っていたのに
消されてしまった
...but he got erased.
かわいそうな悟史君
なんて報われない悟史君
Poor Satoshi-kun.
He got nothing in return.
She's cursed. Go near and you'll
die or be erased by the curse.
あの子は呪われた子
あの子に近づけば
たたりで死ぬかたたりで消えるか
She'll never have peace of mind.
あの子に安らぎなんて あるものか
梨花ちゃんが消えたのも
きっと沙都子のせいだよ！
It's Satoko's fault
that Rika disappeared!
違いない違いない違いない
違いない違いない違いない…
It must be. It must be.
H-Hey, calm down, Mion.
違いない違いない違いない
違いない違いない違いない…
It must be. It must be.
Mi-chan! Keiichi-kun!
（ﾚﾅ）魅ぃちゃん圭一君
I borrowed the key!
鍵借りてきたよ
Oh, good save.
オッ…助かったね
（圭一）あっ…
ねっ？圭ちゃん
Right, Kei-chan?
俺の知っている魅音とは
違う魅音がいるのかもしれない
Maybe there's a different
Mion I don't know about.
At that moment,
I thought that for the first time.
そのとき初めてそう思った
When They Cry
Satoko-chan! Rika-chan!
（ﾚﾅ）沙都子ちゃん梨花ちゃん
いるなら返事して
If you're there, answer me!
Where did they go?
（圭一）どこ行っちまったんだ？
“行った”っていうか…
（圭一･ﾚﾅ）うん？
Nowhere, it seems.
考えたくないけど
I don't want to think this...
村長さんが消えたのが昨日の今日
無関係とは言い切れないね
...but the village headman
disappeared last night.
You can't say it's unrelated.
（圭一）そんな…
No way...
（男性）お～い！
（男性）いたか？
（男性）ダメだこっちは
Is it my fault?
俺のせいなのか…
（ﾚﾅ）圭一君大丈夫？
Are you okay?
俺が全部悪いんだ
It's all my fault.
俺のせいで…
It's my fault...
圭一君…
Keiichi-kun...
“もう子供は家へ帰れ”だって
They're saying the kids
should go home now.
It's my fault
that they disappeared.
俺のせいで消えてしまったんだ
えっ？
どうしてそう思うのかな？かな？
Why do you think
that way? Why?
I know you care about
your friends very much.
圭一君がとても仲間思いだって
知ってるから　だけど…
But I know that it's not your fault.
レナは圭一君のせいじゃ
ないって知ってるよ
圭一君が悪くないって知ってる
I know it's not your fault.
なっ…“知ってる”って…
Y-You know?
I didn't tell Rena.
俺はレナに話してない
圭一君ひょっとして
Are you thinking
that I may disappear too?
レナも消えちゃうんじゃないかって
思ってるのかな？
Then don't worry.
だったら安心して
レナは消えたりしないよ絶対に
I definitely won't disappear.
どうして“消えない”なんて
自信を持って言えるんだよ？
How can you say with
confidence that you won't?
“絶対”なんて…
Definitely...
Mi-chan probably won't
be able to wake up today.
（ﾚﾅ）魅ぃちゃん
さすがに今日は起きられないかもね
あっそっか
Yeah.
She searched all night for the
village headman two nights ago.
おとといの晩も村長さんを捜して
徹夜してるんだよな
Let's go.
行こう
I wonder where
Rika-chan and Satoko went.
（圭一）梨花ちゃんと沙都子
どこ行ったんだろうな？
（ﾚﾅ）
富田(とみた)豆腐店のおばあちゃんがね
The granny from
Tomita Tofu Shop...
昨日学校帰りに
沙都子ちゃんがお店に寄って―
...said she recalls Satoko
coming to buy tofu yesterday...
...on her way back from school.
お豆腐を買っていったのを
覚えてたの
Tofu?
豆腐？
（ﾚﾅ）うん
昨日梨花ちゃん家(ち)では
ガス台にお鍋がかけてあって
Yesterday at Rika's home,
a pot was on the stove...
その中にお味噌汁(みそしる)が入ってたの
...and miso soup was in it.
What does that mean?
それが何だっていうんだ？
You put the tofu in miso
soup at the very, very end.
お味噌汁のお豆腐って
最後の最後に入れるんだよ
That means right up till dinner...
つまり
お料理していた梨花ちゃんは―
お夕飯の直前まであそこに立って
料理していたことになるの
...Rika-chan was
standing there cooking.
（ﾚﾅ）炊飯釜の中も見てみたの
２人分のご飯が炊けていた
I also looked
inside the rice cooker.
There was rice
cooked for two people.
冷蔵庫の中には
手付かずのおかずが何品かあって
There were some untouched
dishes in the fridge...
...which were all wrapped up.
みんなラップがされていた
Um...
え～っと…
ラップって食べ残しとかを
取っておくときにするものだよね
You wrap up leftovers
you want to keep, right?
What do you think that means?
どういうことだと思う？
Um, then they didn't need
to eat anymore or something?
（圭一）えっとじゃ…
夕飯を食べる必要が
なくなって…とか？
All of the sudden too.
（レナ）それも突然にね
前もって分かっていたら
お料理なんか―
If they knew beforehand,
they wouldn't have been cooking.
したりしない
（圭一）えっ？
いなくなったのは
お夕飯ができたあと…
They disappeared after they
finished cooking dinner.
多分７時くらい
Probably around seven.
そんな時間にどこ行ったんだ？
Where'd they go at that time?
Do you recall a soy sauce bottle
and such on the dinner table?
覚えてるかな？
ちゃぶ台の上に―
お醤油(しょうゆ)差しなんかが
置いてあったのを
（ﾚﾅ）
お醤油の小瓶ね空っぽだった
The little soy sauce
bottle was empty.
Checking under the sink...
流しの下を探してみたら
いつもそこに置いてある醤油の
大瓶ごとなくなっていた
...the large bottle of soy sauce
that's usually there was missing.
どういう意味だ？
（ﾚﾅ）ここからは想像だけど
What does that mean?
From this point,
it's just a guess...
...but I think she went to get
soy sauce from the neighbors.
近所に醤油の大瓶を持って
分けてもらいに行ったんだと思うの
沙都子ちゃんは梨花ちゃんが
いつまでたっても帰ってこないから
Since Rika-chan hadn't
come back for a while...
...Satoko-chan called the house
where she went for soy sauce.
醤油を分けてもらいに行った家に
電話をかけた
（沙都子）梨花がそちらに
おジャマしていませんこと？
Did Rika come by your house?
I think they responded like this...
相手は
こんな感じで答えたんだと思う
“うちに食事の用意がしてあるから
沙都子ちゃんもいらっしゃい”
"We have dinner ready, so
you should come over too."
“梨花ちゃんはもう食べてるよ”
"Rika-chan is already eating."
Then where did Rika-chan
go to get soy sauce?
じゃ梨花ちゃんは
どこに醤油をもらいに行ったんだ？
レナの推理はここまで
あくまで想像だから
That's it for my speculation.
It's just a guess after all.
（大石(おおいし)）前原(まえばら)さ～ん
Maebara-san!
（大石）どうも
Hello.
Why are the police here for you?
（ﾚﾅ）
どうして圭一君に警察の人が？
俺は犯人じゃない
（ﾚﾅ）そんなの知ってるよ
I'm not the culprit.
I know.
（圭一）先行ってて
（ﾚﾅ）うん　じゃ
You can go on ahead.
Later.
Are you taking me to the police?
俺を警察に連行するんですか？
No, no.
立ち話も何ですから車の中で
お話ししようってだけですよ
I just thought we could talk in the
car instead of standing around.
（圭一）…で捜査のほうは
どうなってるんです？
So how's the investigation going?
捜査？何のです？
Investigation? For what?
最近はいっぱいありすぎて
どれのことやら
There've been too
many lately. Which one?
全部です！
（大石）ああ全部ね
All of them.
Oh, all of them.
Tomitake-san and Takano-san's
cases went cold, unfortunately.
富竹さんと鷹野さんの件は
恥ずかしながらさっぱりです
What about the village headman?
Did you find any clues?
村長さんのほうはどうなんですか
何か手がかりはありました？
足取りはつかんだんですがね
行方不明になった一昨日は―
We've traced his steps.
In the morning two days
ago when he went missing...
朝イチで鹿骨(ししぼね)市内の某大学病院の
肛門科にお忍びで行っています
...he secretly saw a proctologist at
a university hospital in Shishibone.
Proctologist?
肛門科？
（大石）
ええ家族にも誰にもナイショでね
Yes, he kept it secret
from his family and others.
プライドが許さんのでしょう
肛門科だなんて
Probably didn't want to hurt
his ego, a proctologist and all...
…で
帰り道電車の事故があったようで
There was a train
accident on his way back...
家に帰ってすぐ
神社の会合に駆け込んだそうです
...so he went to the meeting at
the shrine right after returning.
What's wrong?
Does something bother you?
（大石）どうしました？
何か引っ掛かります？
いや…
No...
（詩音）私昨日打ち明けたんです
公由のおじいちゃんに
Yesterday, I told
gramps Kimiyoshi everything.
それはいつだ？
When was that?
（詩音）じゃ言いますね…
Then I'll tell you...
I heard Tomitake-san and
Takano-san died last night.
ゆうべ富竹さんと
鷹野さんが死んだそうです
The village headman
disappeared two days ago.
村長さんが
いなくなったのはおととい
Shion heard about Tomitake-san
and Takano-san in the morning.
詩音が鷹野さんと富竹さんのことを
聞いたのもおとといの朝
But the village headman
secretly went to the hospital.
でも村長さんは朝イチに
誰にもナイショで病院に行っている
I told him yesterday.
（詩音）昨日打ち明けたんです
詩音はいつ打ち明けた？
When did Shion tell him?
Maebara-san? Maebara-san?
（大石）前原さん前原さん
いいですか？私は別にあなたが
犯人だなんて思っていません
Listen, I don't necessarily
think you're the culprit.
あの晩あなたたち４人が―
I know the four of you snuck into
the ritual tool shrine that night.
あの祭具殿に
忍び込んだことは知っています
次の日には
もうウワサになっていましたからね
It was already a rumor
by the next day.
それ自体は
不法侵入として問われるべきですが
For that itself, you should be
interrogated for trespassing...
問題はそんなことではなく
そこに何があったかなんです
...but the question
is what was in there.
Something that explains why those
who sneak in keep getting killed.
忍び込んだ人間が
次々と犠牲になるような何か
There were a lot of torture
tools from a long time ago.
大昔に使った拷問道具が
たくさんしまってありました
Is that all?
それだけ？
（圭一）はいそれだけです
Yes, that's it.
There wasn't something horrible
hidden that'd force your silence?
口封じをされるような
とんでもない物が―
隠してあったんじゃないですか？
No, there really
wasn't anything else.
いや 本当に ほかには何も
ふむ…
ではあなただけが見なかった―
Then maybe there was
something that you didn't see.
何かがあったのか…
（圭一）えっ？
私が知りたいのは―
What I want to know
is why you're safe...
あなただけが無事で
ほかの３人が被害に遭った
...while the other
three were harmed.
I want to know
what's so different.
そこにどんな違いが
あったのかってことなんです
ちょっと待ってください
“あなただけが”って…
Wait a minute.
Only me? What do you
mean by the other three?
“ほかの３人”って
どういう意味ですか？
Takano-san and
Tomitake-san and...
鷹野さんと富竹さんと…
ハハハハッ…ですから
鷹野さんと富竹さんが死に―
I'm saying Takano-san
and Tomitake-san died...
園崎詩音さんが失踪しました
...and Shion
Sonozaki-san went missing.
あなただけが
無事に今日まで過ごしているんです
Only you are still living
unharmed up till today.
S-Shion went missing?
し…詩音が失踪？
I'm saying Takano-san
and Tomitake-san died...
（大石）ですから
鷹野さんと富竹さんが死に―
園崎詩音さんが失踪しました
...and Shion
Sonozaki-san went missing.
Hello?
（詩音）あっ圭ちゃんですか？
私です詩音です
Oh, Kei-chan? It's me, Shion.
Did you hear about
Rika and Satoko?
聞いたか？
梨花ちゃんと沙都子の件
ええ…結局
あのあとどうなったんですか？
Yes, what happened after that?
Were they found?
見つかったんですか？
（圭一）見つからなかった
They weren't found.
Kei-chan, please don't feel bad.
圭ちゃん…
どうか気を落とさないでください
（圭一）受話器の向こうのこいつが
完璧(かんぺき)に詩音であればあるほど―
The more I think the person on
the other end is actually Shion...
...the more scared I get.
恐ろしさが募っていく
This isn't Shion.
Who is this person?
こいつは詩音じゃない…
こいつは一体何者なんだ？
When...
いつ…
When did you tell him everything?
いつ打ち明けたんだよ？
（詩音）えっ？
村長さんは痔(じ)を患っていて
病院にかかっていたのを知ってるか
Did you know he had hemorrhoids
and was going to the hospital?
I knew he had hemorrhoids
since he was in pain when he sat.
痔だったのは知っています
座るときとかつらそうでしたから
Then which hospital did he go to?
じゃどこの病院に通ってたかは？
ごめんなさい
それはちょっと知りませんけど
Sorry, I don't know that.
でも圭ちゃんそれが一体何の？
But why does
that matter, Kei-chan?
詩音は病院を知らない
…ということは―
She doesn't know the hospital.
Then going to the hospital
to tell him isn't possible.
病院まで押しかけていって
打ち明けるなんてことは不可能だ
村長さんが帰ってきたのは
電車の事故でギリギリの時間
He barely came back in time
because of the train accident.
会合に間に合うためには―
To make his meeting, he had no
time to listen to her confession.
詩音の打ち明け話に
つきあってる時間はないはず
When did you tell
the village headman everything?
詩音は
いつ村長さんに打ち明けたんだ？
Kei-chan, why are you
asking me such a thing?
圭ちゃん… なんで そんなことを？
朝に
村長さんをつかまえるのはムリだ
You couldn't have
caught him in the morning.
詩音も一緒に会合に出たのか？
Did you also attend the meeting?
いやそれはありえない　だって…
No, that's impossible.
Because...
園崎詩音は…
...Shion Sonozaki went missing
the day after the cotton drifting!
綿流しの翌日失踪したんだ！
Please, if what I said
is wrong, tell me so.
頼む
俺が言ったことが間違ってるなら
そうだと言ってくれ
Shion, please!
詩音頼むから…
Shion, you didn't
see the village headman.
詩音お前は
村長に会ってなんかいないんだ
If you did, it would've
been after his meeting.
もし会ったとしたなら―
村長が会合を終えたあと
すなわち失踪する直前
That is, right before
he went missing, or...
もしくは…
It has to be after
he went missing!
失踪してからしかありえないんだ
To get my happiness,
I had done everything...
...but had done nothing
to be blamed and accused of.
The sound of footsteps
became louder every day.
Then I noticed the fact
there was no time.
I was a believer in life,
to be myself always.
And was asking
whether I would be alive.
Give me a reason
why not to adopt in this way.
Or judge me to be guilty
of so many incurable sins.
Tell me why or why not?
Complaining way too much.
Maybe I overlooked
something fatal for me.
Preview
A regret you cannot end.
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
終わらせることのできない後悔
A story that will never apologize.
謝ることのない物語
そこに刻まれているのは
もう１人の私
What is engraved
there is the other me.
When They Cry.
「ひぐらしのなく頃に」
"Cotton Drifting" Chapter,
Episode 4: WISH.
- "Cotton Drifting" Chapter -
Episode 04: WISH
"Cotton Drifting" Chapter,
Episode 4: WISH.
- "Cotton Drifting" Chapter -
Episode 04: WISH
Can you believe it?
あなたは信じられますか？